## **Quinn Lashinsky**

7303 Bristol Drive, Union, NJ 07083 C:973-634-7866 guinnlashinsky@gmail.com

### SUMMARY

Coffee professional with a combined 5 years of experience in creation, preparation, and deliverance of exceptional coffee beverages with outstanding service. Quick learner with a meticulous attention to detail and excellent written and oral communication skills. Works well with others cultivating relationships that create a better work environment.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Pantry Manager/Barista WeWork HQ Chelsea

Nov 2015 - Present New York City, NY

- Made 400+ drinks a day handling the barista bar by myself
- 50+ hours a week
- In charge of ordering coffee goods and pantry supplies

# Lead Barista/Barista La Colombe NY

Nov 2015 - August 2017 Philadelphia, PA/New York City,

- Food Handlers certified
  - Responsible for maintaining steady workflow completing 140+ transactions per hour, per shift
  - Training new employees on the ins and outs of bar service and how to be quick and efficient
  - Received espresso, milk, and general cafe training from National Trainer in New York and Regional Trainer in Philadelphia
  - Worked with the Workshop Roasters by participating in cuppings, discussions on roasting and packaging coffee.
  - Extensive knowledge of the breadth of La Colombe coffee offerings
  - Skilled in hot and cold beverage preparation
  - Dedication to furthering specialty coffee knowledge through a combination of research and hands-on experience
  - Willing to go the extra mile to ensure customers have a fantastic, engaging experience

# Barista OCF Coffeehouse Fairmount

May 2015 - Nov 2015 Philadelphia, PA

- Received espresso and coffee training from Square One Coffee
- ServSafe certified

Education

Bachelor of Arts, Theater, conc. Musical Theatre